Sharpay's Fabulous Adventure is a family, music
film directed by Michael Lembeck.
After a talent scout spots her performing with her dog Boi at a charity gala, Sharpay Evans sets
off for the bright lights of NYC, convinced instant fame and fortune are in the bag.
But theatre's a dog-eat-dog world.
Fortunately, Sharpay also meets Peyton, a handsome student filmmaker who
finds Sharpay nearly as fascinating as she finds herself.
Sharpay Evans, played by Ashley French.
Peyton Leverett, played by Austin Butler.
Amber Lee Adams, played by Cameron Goodman.
Roger Elliston the Third, played by Bradley Steven Perry.
Gill Samms, played by Alec Mapa.
Neal Roberts, played by Jack Plotnick.
Sharpay's Fabulous Adventure is a 2011 American direct-to-video musical romantic
comedy film and High School Musical spin-off starring Ashley Tisdale.
Set a year after the events of High School Musical 3: Senior Year (2008), the film centers on
Sharpay Evans' life after graduation and her efforts to obtain a role in a Broadway show.
Sharpay's Fabulous Adventure was released as a
Blu-ray/DVD combo pack on April 19, 2011.
It then premiered as a Disney Channel Original Movie
on Disney Channel on May 22, 2011.
It is the only Disney Channel Original Movie to be released on
home media before being broadcast on Disney Channel.
The film explores themes of new york city, human animal
relationship, musical, rivalry, spin off.